Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Material for Publications and Exhibitions, 1901-2003; Series III; 17.7 linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts
    - Volume 3, 1973-1989 (Box 82)
      "Sacramento City During the Flood of 1862"
      "Selected Readings Concerning the History of Women in Photography"
      "Silver Plates by the Golden Gate: A Brief History of the Daguerreotype in San Francisco"
      "Soule's California Stereographs"
      "Stereo Photography On the Rise"
      "The Stereo Daguerreotype in San Francisco: A Short and Unsuccessful Career"
      "Stereo Photography in the California Redwoods"
      "What is a Western Photographer?"
      "Women Photographers in California Before 1901"
      "Yosemite's First Stereo Photographer -- Charles Leander Weed"
  - Drafts and Mock-ups
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Humboldt State College, Sequoia Theater, brochure, mock-up, 1963 (Box 83)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Humboldt State College, Division of Natural Resources, brochure, mock-up, circa 1965 (Box 84)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "Peter Britt and His Media," lecture transcript, 1976 November 30 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "The California Indian in Three-Dimensional Photography," draft, circa 1979 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "Photographic Archeology: A Case for Regional Study," draft, circa 1984 (Box 85)
    - CAL-PHOTO: Journal of California Photographic History, mock-up, circa 1989 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Camera Fiends & Kodak Girls: 50 Selections By and About Women in Photography, 1840-1930, mock-up photocopy, circa 1989 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "(Uncorrected Laundry List of My) Résumé of Photographic History, 1971-1996", circa 1996 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Nellie Ladd: Photographs of Old Denny, California, 1895-1920, galleys, circa 1999 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., and Gia Musso, Behind the Redwood Curtain, mock-up, circa 1999 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., A Collector's Obsession: Photographs of Humboldt County, California from the Peter E. Palmquist Collection, mock-up, circa 2001 (Box 86)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., and Pam Mendelsohn, Grace Chandler Photographs, 1908-1928, galleys, circa 2002 (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "Collecting Regional Photography," draft, undated (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., "Photography is Everywhere Today," draft, undated (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Untitled book on tintypes, mock-up, undated (Box 85)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., Photographing the Humboldt County Redwoods, mock-up, undated (Box 87)
  - Unrealized Projects
    Drafts, research files, correspondence, and other material related to unrealized projects by Palmquist and his collaborators.
    Organized under ten headings: Back to Front; Cover Girls; Directory of 19th Century California Photographers; The Evolvement of Commercial Photography in San Francisco, 1849 to 1865; A Journey into the Archive; Photographers and Their Equipment; Robert H. Vance Essay; Snap Judgment; Women Photography; and Voices from the Craft.
    - Back to Front
      Unrealized project exploring portrait photographs that depict the front and back of the subject.
      - Illustrations, 10 folders (Box 88)
    - Cover Girls
      Preliminary research for an unrealized project that collected magazine covers with photographs created by women photographers. Material includes copy photographs and photocopies of magazine covers, as well as biographical information.
      - Proposal (Box 89)
      - Inventory (Box 89)
      - Essay (Box 89)
      - Photographers
        - Acevedo, Melanie (Box 89)
        - Albert, Jade (Box 89)
        - Alberts, Andrea (Box 89)
        - Allen, Frances Stebbins (Box 89)
        - Arian, Patricia (Box 89)
        - Arnold, Harriet (Box 89)
        - Ashworth, E. M. (Box 89)
        - Aurbach, Ellen (Box 89)
        - Bourke-White, Margaret (Box 89)
      - 1900-1940 (Box 89)
      - 1940-1970 (Box 89)
      - 1970-1990 (Box 89)
      - 1990-2000 (Box 89)
      - Life magazine covers by women photographers (Box 89)
      - Photographic negatives and contact prints (Box 89)
    - Directory of 19th Century California Photographers
      Preliminary drafts of an unrealized directory of photographers in California, 1850-1900.
      - Palmquist, Peter E., "California Photographers: A Bibliographic Reference and Listing of Photographers Active in California Prior to 1900", 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Front Matter, 1988 June (Box 90)
      - Index and listing of photographers active in California before 1900 (Box 90)
      - A, 1990 June; 3 folders (Box 90)
      - B, 1989 March; 3 folders (Box 90)
      - Ba (Box 90)
      - Ca, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Illustrations, A-B (Box 90)
    - The Evolvement of Commercial Photography in San Francisco, 1849 to 1865
      Correspondence and research material related to an unrealized article by Palmquist and Robert B. Fisher that chronologically and spatially located early photography studios in San Francisco, California.
      - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 91)
      - Drafts, 1995 June 5, undated; 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Chronology for George Robinson Fardon, James A. Clayton, Robert H. Vance, Carleton E. Watkins, and James May Ford, 1849-1867, 1992 June (Box 91)
      - Chronological list of San Francisco photographers' studio locations, 1849-1865 (Box 91)
      - San Francisco gallery locations, 1849-1865 (Box 91)
    - A Journey into the Archive
      Organized under three headings: Drafts, Draft Essays, and Correspondence.
      Material related to an unrealized collection of essays with the working title of "A Journey into the Archive," organized by Palmquist and guest edited by Rebekah Burgess, which sought to review books by and about women photographers with work represented in the collection of the Women in Photography Archive.
      - Drafts
        - Project description (Box 92)
        - Meteyard, Eliza (Box 92)
        - Layout (Box 92)
        - Introduction (Box 92)
        - Appendix, Books in the Women in Photography Archive (Box 92)
      - Draft Essays
        - Clendaniel, Nancy (Box 92)
        - Dalrymple, Marilyn (Box 92)
        - Glauber, Carol (Box 92)
        - Gordon, Anna Pegler (Box 92)
        - Gillian Greenhill-Hannum (Box 92)
        - Hendrickson (Box 92)
        - Ihara, Rachel (Box 92)
        - Lamuniere, Michelle (Box 92)
        - McCarroll, Stacey (Box 92)
        - Mooney, Cassandra (Box 92)
        - Musso, Gia (Box 92)
        - Rule, Amy (Box 92)
        - Samuels, Ainlay, 2 folders (Box 92)
        - Saretzky, Gary (Box 92)
        - Watts, Jenny (Box 92)
      - Correspondence
        - Clendaniel, Nancy (Box 92)
        - Dalrymple, Marilyn (Box 92)
        - Gordon, Anna Pegler (Box 92)
        - Glauber, Carole (Box 92)
        - Greenhill, Gillian Hannum (Box 92)
        - Hendrickson, Linnea (Box 92)
        - Lamuniere, Michelle (Box 92)
        - McCarroll, Stacey (Box 92)
        - Musso, Gia (Box 92)
        - Rule, Amy (Box 92)
        - Samuels, Ainlay (Box 92)
        - Sartezky, Gary (Box 92)
        - Watts, Jenny (Box 92)
        - Correspondence updates (Box 92)
    - Photographers and Their Equipment
      Material related to an unrealized book, "Photographers and Their Equipment," which planned to include photographic depictions of photographers with their equipment, including cameras, dark tents, and studio apparatuses, as well as advertsing and studio backmarks.
      - Book draft (Box 93)
      - Research Files
        - Abell, Frank G. (Box 94)
        - Adams, Ansel (Box 94)
        - Addis, A. S. (Box 94)
        - Alisky, Charles (Box 94)
        - Anderson, C. H. (Box 94)
        - Anderson, G. E. (Box 94)
        - Anderson, John A. (Box 94)
        - Andrews, T. P. (Box 94)
        - Anthony, Edward (Box 94)
        - Archer, Fred R. (Box 94)
        - Arnold, R. J. (Box 94)
        - Arnold, William T. (Box 94)
        - Art-Ray (Box 94)
        - Asbeck, A. (Box 94)
        - Bacon, Frank (Box 94)
        - Baker, Geo. H. (Box 94)
        - Baker, J. W. (Box 94)
        - Baker, Isaac (Box 94)
        - Backus (Box 94)
        - Barber, W. B. (Box 94)
        - Barnett (Box 94)
        - Bast, W. (Box 94)
        - Batchelder, B. P. (Box 94)
        - Batchelder, P. M. (Box 94)
        - Bayley & Winter (Box 94)
        - Beals, H. S. (Box 94)
        - Beatty, D. D. (Box 94)
        - Bell, C. (Box 94)
        - Bell, W. A. (Box 94)
        - Bergeron & Gatliff (Box 94)
        - Best Studio (Box 94)
        - Bierstadt, Charles (Box 94)
        - Billington, W. C. (Box 94)
        - Birch, Billy (Actor), fake photographer (Box 94)
        - Black, Alfred E. (Box 94)
        - Blum, Robt. F. (Box 94)
        - Bodine, H. Oliver (Box 94)
        - Bonine, E. A. (Box 94)
        - Bowman, R. H. (Box 94)
        - Bowman, W. S. (Box 94)
        - Boye, Otto (Box 94)
        - Boysen, J. T. (Box 94)
        - Bradley, Henry (Box 94)
        - Brady, Mathew (Box 94)
        - Brewster J. C. (Box 94)
        - Brigandi, Philip (Box 94)
        - Brince, Herman (Box 94)
        - Britt, Peter (Box 94)
        - Brown, T. A. (Box 94)
        - Bruton, Geo. D. (Box 94)
        - Burgers, Walt (Box 94)
        - Burgess, A. A. (Box 94)
        - Burkett, Clarence (Box 94)
        - Bundy, O. C. (Box 94)
        - Burnham, S. W. (Box 94)
        - Bush, Henry (Box 94)
        - Bush, J. L. (Box 94)
        - Bushnell (Box 94)
        - California Camera Club (Box 94)
        - California School of Photography (Box 94)
        - Cameron, J. (Box 94)
        - Campbell, Hamilton (Box 94)
        - Campbell, W. B. (Box 94)
        - Cantwell, H. C. (Box 94)
        - Canepa, Peter (Box 94)
        - Cannon, Marsena (Box 94)
        - Carden, R. A. (Box 94)
        - Carpenter, A. O. & Family (Box 94)
        - Carpenter, J. C. (Box 94)
        - Carr, Richard (Box 94)
        - Carter, C. W. (Box 94)
        - Carvalho, Solomon (Box 94)
        - Castleman, Philip F. (Box 94)
        - Castro y Ordonez, Rafael (Box 94)
        - Chamberlain, W. G. (Box 94)
        - Chamley, Stephen Fred (Box 94)
        - Chase, Ed (Box 94)
        - Churchman Bros. (Box 94)
        - Clark Photo Co. (Box 94)
        - Clayton, J. A. (Box 94)
        - Clearwater, Ida and Bob (Box 94)
        - Cliff Photo Gallery (Box 94)
        - Clifford, G. (Box 94)
        - Clinch, W. A. (Box 94)
        - Coffin, I. T. (Box 94)
        - Colby, Howard (Box 94)
        - Conaway, B. F. (Box 94)
        - Connell, Will (Box 94)
        - Cook, J. J. (Box 94)
        - Coombs, A. C. (Box 94)
        - Coon, Floyd (Box 94)
        - Couse -Baker, Robt. (Box 94)
        - Crawford, E. L. (Box 94)
        - Cressy, Capt. J. P. (Box 94)
        - Crockwell, James H. (Box 94)
        - Crook, William H. (Box 94)
        - Cunningham, A. C. (Box 94)
        - Curtis, C. C. (Box 94)
        - Curtis, Edward S. (Box 94)
        - Daguerre (Box 94)
        - Dall, John (Box 94)
        - Dames, W. W. (Box 94)
        - Dames & Dorsaz (Box 94)
        - Davidson, I. G. (Box 94)
        - Davis, Phinas A. (Box 94)
        - De Long, Charles E. (Box 94)
        - D'Estrella, T. H. (Box 94)
        - De Plongue, Louis (Box 94)
        - Deu Vaul (Box 94)
        - Dewitt & Hartez (Box 94)
        - D' H. (Box 94)
        - Dickman, Charles (Box 94)
        - Donnel, J. W. (Box 94)
        - Dornin, G. D. (Box 94)
        - Dorrothy, Harry S. (Box 94)
        - Dowe, A. W. (Box 94)
        - Downey, William M. & Son (Box 94)
        - Downing, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Duhem, Victor M (Box 94)
        - Dunham & Lathrop (Box 94)
        - Dusy, Frank (Box 94)
        - Eastman, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Ebell, Adrian J. (Box 94)
        - Edgerton, H. H. (Box 94)
        - Edouart (Box 94)
        - Eisen, E. G., Dr. (Box 94)
        - Eldridge, J. E. (Box 94)
        - Elite (Box 94)
        - Ericson, A. W. (Box 94)
        - Erwin, J. W. (Box 94)
        - Ette, Oscar (Box 94)
        - Eureka Photo & Art (Box 94)
        - Fagersteen, Gustav (Box 94)
        - Fardon, G. R. (Box 94)
        - Fassold, Peter (Box 94)
        - Fiske, Geo. (Box 94)
        - Fitch, Herbert R. (Box 94)
        - Fitzgibbon, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Flaglor, A. P. (Box 94)
        - Fletcher, Capt. R. H. (Box 94)
        - Ford, J. M. (Box 94)
        - Forsmark (Box 94)
        - Fortune, E. W. (Box 94)
        - Foster, Geo. H. (Box 94)
        - Fowzer, George (Box 94)
        - Fowzer, Jacob (Box 94)
        - Franklin, M. A. (Box 94)
        - Franklin & Howell (Box 94)
        - Frasher, Burton Sr. (Box 94)
        - Freeman, Ed (Box 94)
        - French, Ira G. (Box 94)
        - Froehlic, Herb (Box 94)
        - Gage, H. K. (Box 94)
        - Garden City Photo Co. (Box 94)
        - Garreh, Edwin (Box 94)
        - Gatliff (Box 94)
        - Genthe, Arnold (Box 94)
        - Get, Fong (Box 94)
        - Gilbert, G. H. (Box 94)
        - Gilchrist, Neil (Box 94)
        - Gill, Frank (Box 94)
        - Gillard, Rudy (Box 94)
        - Godeus, J. D. (Box 94)
        - Godfrey, William M. (Box 94)
        - Goebel, R. (Box 94)
        - Golden Rule Bazaar (Box 94)
        - Grant, M. H. (Box 94)
        - Gregor, A. (Box 94)
        - Habenicht, Geo. (Box 94)
        - Halsey (Box 94)
        - Halsey & Coffin (Box 94)
        - Hamilton, C. F. (Box 94)
        - Hammersmith, John E. (Box 94)
        - Hansen, Jacob (Box 94)
        - Harris, W. (Box 94)
        - Hart, A. A. (Box 94)
        - Haussler (Box 94)
        - Haynes, F. J. (Box 94)
        - Hayward (Box 94)
        - Hazeltine, M. M. (Box 94)
        - Heath, Chas E. (Box 94)
        - Hedger & Noe (Box 94)
        - Heering, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Heller, Louis (Box 94)
        - Hemingway & Holmes (Box 94)
        - Hendee Bros. (Box 94)
        - Henriod (Box 94)
        - Hicks, John Ross (Box 94)
        - Hicks, L. D. (Box 94)
        - Higgins, T. J. (Box 94)
        - Hill, A. P. (Box 94)
        - Hillers (Box 94)
        - Hillyer (Box 94)
        - Hirsch & Kaiser (Box 94)
        - Hodson, Burton (Box 94)
        - Hodson, J. R. (Box 94)
        - Hogan, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Hogg, Jabez (Box 94)
        - Holdens Drugs-Stockton (Box 94)
        - Holmes, Alex (Box 94)
        - Holmes, R. R. R. (Box 94)
        - Houseworth (Box 94)
        - Howell, A. W. (Box 94)
        - Howe, C. W. (Box 94)
        - Howland (Box 94)
        - Howland, Benjamin F. (Box 94)
        - Howland, C. A. (Box 94)
        - Howland & Lonergan (Box 94)
        - Hulbert, Neil K. (Box 94)
        - Humboldt Studio (Box 94)
        - Hutching, J. H. (Box 94)
        - Imperial (Box 94)
        - Ingersoll, W. B. (Box 94)
        - Jackson, W. H. (Box 94)
        - Jacobs, J. M. (Box 94)
        - Jacoby, W. H (Box 94)
        - James, G. W. (Box 94)
        - Jarvis, Benjamin (Box 94)
        - Jarvis, Lucius (Box 94)
        - Jellum (Box 94)
        - Jezler, Carl Lucas (Box 94)
        - Johnson, Albert J. (Box 94)
        - Johnson, Craig (Box 94)
        - Johnson, C. E. (Box 94)
        - Johnson, C. W. J. (Box 94)
        - Johnson, Edward (Box 94)
        - Johnson, G. H. (Box 94)
        - Johnson, Josiah Jr. (Box 94)
        - Johnson & Sullivan (Box 94)
        - Johnston, J. W. (Box 94)
        - Johnston & Howes (Box 94)
        - Jones, Edward (Box 94)
        - Jones, John Wesley (Box 94)
        - Jordan (Box 94)
        - Jorgenson's studio (Box 94)
        - Judkins (Box 94)
        - Kemp, E. H. (Box 94)
        - KIEM-TV (Box 94)
        - Kilbourne (Box 94)
        - Kilburn Bros. (Box 94)
        - Kilburn Kenny (Box 94)
        - King Bros. (Box 94)
        - Kinsey, Darius (Box 94)
        - Kipps, A. K. (Box 94)
        - Klain, N. M. (Box 94)
        - Klein, Ron (Box 94)
        - Knight, Tom (Box 94)
        - Knight & Perkins (Box 94)
        - Kusel, E. A. (Box 94)
        - Lancey, Thomas Crosby (Box 95)
        - Lange, O. V. (Box 95)
        - Langenheim Bros. (Box 95)
        - Lanier, Chas. (Box 95)
        - Lare, C. A. (Box 95)
        - Larson, P. E. (Box 95)
        - Larss & Duclos (Box 95)
        - Laval (Box 95)
        - Lawrence, G. R. (Box 95)
        - Lawrence & Houseworth (Box 95)
        - Lees, Isaiah (Box 95)
        - Le Plongeon (Box 95)
        - Liebert, A. (Box 95)
        - Littleton View Co. (Box 95)
        - Logan, C. W. (Box 95)
        - Long, Enoch (Box 95)
        - Longpré, Paul de (Box 95)
        - Loomis, A. W. (Box 95)
        - Loomis, B. F. (Box 95)
        - Loryea & MaCauley (Box 95)
        - Los Angeles Camera Club (Box 95)
        - Lothers (Box 95)
        - Lovejoy, William (Box 95)
        - Lukens, Theodore (Box 95)
        - Lummis, C. F. (Box 95)
        - Mains, J. R. (Box 95)
        - Marceau, Theo C. (Box 95)
        - Martin, Covert (Box 95)
        - Maude, F. H. (Box 95)
        - Maxwell, John Franklin (Box 95)
        - Matthews, H. E. (Box 95)
        - McCafferty (Box 95)
        - McClees & Germon (Box 95)
        - McCloskey, J. J. (Box 95)
        - McCullagh, E. J. (Box 95)
        - McCurry & Co. (Box 95)
        - McFarland, A. G. (Box 95)
        - McIntyre, S. C. (Box 95)
        - McKean & Ort (Box 95)
        - McLeod (Box 95)
        - Meddaugh (Box 95)
        - Meiser, Jesse (Box 95)
        - Melander, Silas (Box 95)
        - Merriam, Ezra D. (Box 95)
        - Meyer, C. A. (Box 95)
        - Michaels, V. (Box 95)
        - Middlemiss, B. (Box 95)
        - Miller, Jesse (Box 95)
        - Miller, Milton M. (Box 95)
        - Monaco, J. B. (Box 95)
        - Monaco, Louis (Box 95)
        - Monaco, Marino (Box 95)
        - Moore, A. C. (Box 95)
        - Morphy, W. F. (Box 95)
        - Morrison, M. M. (Box 95)
        - Morse, G. D. (Box 95)
        - Mortenson, William (Box 95)
        - Morton, Laurence B. (Box 95)
        - Mullen, Chester (Box 95)
        - Mullender, D. F. or Joseph? (Box 95)
        - Muybridge, E. J. (Box 95)
        - Nahl Bros. (Box 95)
        - Nelson, C. A. (Box 95)
        - Nesemann, Enno (Box 95)
        - Noe, Miguel (Box 95)
        - Norcross (Box 95)
        - O'Connor, D. L. (Box 95)
        - Oliphant, W. J. (Box 95)
        - Ormsby, E. D. (Box 95)
        - O'Sullivan, T. H. (Box 95)
        - Ottinger, George (Box 95)
        - Overton (Box 95)
        - Owings, J. J. (Box 95)
        - Palace Studio (Box 95)
        - Palmer (Box 95)
        - Palmer, W. E. (Box 95)
        - Palmquist, P. E. (Box 95)
        - Parker (Box 95)
        - Parker, Jonathan (Box 95)
        - Parsons, D. H. (Box 95)
        - Partridge, J. E. (Box 95)
        - Partridge, Roi (Box 95)
        - Patterson, Frank (Box 95)
        - Payne, H. T. (Box 95)
        - Peterson, Lowell M. (Box 95)
        - Peabody, Henry G. (Box 95)
        - Penelon (Box 95)
        - Perry, Ira C. (Box 95)
        - Petzval, Dr. Joseph (Box 95)
        - Phegley, J. W. (Box 95)
        - Philips, Denver (Box 95)
        - Photographer's Association of California (Box 95)
        - Photo Specialty Shop (Box 95)
        - Piatt, W. J. (Box 95)
        - Pickett, J. M. (Box 95)
        - Pierce, C. C. (Box 95)
        - Pillsbury, Arthur, C. (Box 95)
        - Plumbe, John (Box 95)
        - Pollock (Box 95)
        - Pond, C. L. (Box 95)
        - Power, H. D'arcy, Dr. (Box 95)
        - Price, Andrew (Box 95)
        - Rankin, G. W. (Box 95)
        - Rau, William (Box 95)
        - Rea & Rauscher, 3rd St. Gallery (Box 95)
        - Reed, C. E. (Box 95)
        - Reed, G. W. (Box 95)
        - Reed & Co. (Box 95)
        - Reilly, J. J. (Box 95)
        - Reynolds, Ernest M. (Box 95)
        - Robinson, Frank D. (Box 95)
        - Roche, T. C. (Box 95)
        - Rogers, C. T. (Box 95)
        - Ross, Geo (Box 95)
        - Royal Photographic Studio (Box 95)
        - Rulofson, W. H. (Box 95)
        - Ryder, Charles A. (Box 95)
        - Ryder, James (Box 95)
        - Sammis, E. M. (Box 95)
        - Samuels, M. A. (Box 95)
        - San Diego Camera Club (Box 95)
        - Santa Clara Gallery (Box 95)
        - Savage, C. R. (Box 95)
        - Schellenberg, M. O. (Box 95)
        - Schiller, Rudolph N. (Box 95)
        - Schoeme (Box 95)
        - Schubert, G. H. (Box 95)
        - Schuffler, C. M. (Box 95)
        - Schultz (Box 95)
        - Schumacher, F. G. (Box 95)
        - Schumacher, Leo (Box 95)
        - Scripture, J. C. (Box 95)
        - Seely (Box 95)
        - Selleck, Silas (Box 95)
        - Sewell (Box 95)
        - Shaw, Seth Louis (Box 95)
        - Shaw, Stephen Williams (Box 95)
        - Shaw, William (Box 95)
        - Shew, Jacob (Box 95)
        - Shew, Myron (Box 95)
        - Shew, W. (Box 95)
        - Shipler (Box 95)
        - Shipley, J. W. (Box 95)
        - Shuster, Merle (Box 95)
        - Silver, O. B. (Box 95)
        - Silvis, J. B. (Box 95)
        - Smaus, Louis A. (Box 95)
        - Smith, A. L. (Box 95)
        - Smith, Gary D. (Box 95)
        - Smith, William Horace (Box 95)
        - Sohon, G. (Box 95)
        - Song, W. F. (Box 95)
        - Soule, J. P. (Box 95)
        - Soracco (Box 95)
        - Southworth, A. S. (Box 95)
        - Spesert, Edwin Allis (Box 95)
        - Spesert, George Francis (Box 95)
        - Splane, C. V. (Box 95)
        - Spooner, J. P. (Box 95)
        - Stanton, T. E. (Box 95)
        - Stellman, Louis J. (Box 95)
        - Stephans, John L. (Box 95)
        - Stone, Bruce (Box 95)
        - Street, Richard Steven (Box 95)
        - Street, W. J. (Box 95)
        - Strong, J. D. (Box 95)
        - Strong, M. H. (Box 95)
        - Strong, N. B. (Box 95)
        - Strong, R. W. (Box 95)
        - Strong, W. K. (Box 95)
        - Stuart, W. M. (Box 95)
        - Sutterley Bros. (Box 95)
        - Swadley, W. W. (Box 95)
        - Swanlund, Oscar (Box 95)
        - Swanlund, Sam (Box 95)
        - Swazey, Ben (Box 95)
        - Swazey, Fred (Box 95)
        - Symons, Charles W. (Box 95)
        - Taber, I. W. (Box 95)
        - Terkelson, L. F. (Box 95)
        - Terkelson and Henry (Box 95)
        - Thomas, C. N. (Box 95)
        - Thompson, H. (Box 95)
        - Thompson, J. G. (Box 95)
        - Thors (Box 95)
        - Tolles, Ron (Box 95)
        - Tower Photo Co. (Box 95)
        - Towne, Paul (Box 95)
        - Train, E. H. (Box 95)
        - Treat, A. J. (Box 95)
        - Treat, ?. R. (Box 95)
        - Tucker (Box 95)
        - Turrill, Chas. B. (Box 95)
        - Tuttle, C. K. (Box 95)
        - Twogood, Fred W. (Box 95)
        - Vale, W. A. (Box 95)
        - Valleau, Geo. (Box 95)
        - Vance, R. H. (Box 95)
        - Vance, William (Box 95)
        - Vandiveer and Porter (Box 95)
        - Vansant, J. (Box 95)
        - Vansant, W. P. (Box 95)
        - Vaissade, Ben (Box 95)
        - Van Court, James (Box 95)
        - Vaughan, H. G. (Box 95)
        - Vaughan, H. W. (Box 95)
        - Vischer, Ed (Box 95)
        - Voightlander (Box 95)
        - Waite, C. B. (Box 95)
        - Wakely, Geo. D. (Box 95)
        - Waters, R. J. (Box 95)
        - Watkins, Carleton E., 4 folders (Box 95)
        - Watson, Orrin (Box 95)
        - Wax, William (Box 95)
        - Weaver, Miles (Box 95)
        - Webster, F. A. (Box 95)
        - Webster, W. B. (Box 95)
        - Weed, C. L. (Box 95)
        - Weingarth (Box 95)
        - Wells and Sears (Box 95)
        - Weston (Box 95)
        - White, H. C. (Box 95)
        - Wigham, R. P. (Box 95)
        - Wilcox, Geo. L. (Box 95)
        - Williams (Box 95)
        - Williams, H. E. (Box 95)
        - Willis and Hamilton (Box 95)
        - William, S. M. (Box 95)
        - Wilson (Box 95)
        - Wilson, Doug (Box 95)
        - Winberg, J. A. (Box 95)
        - Wolf, Willie (Box 95)
        - Wolfenstein (Box 95)